After Ever Happy is a romance, drama film directed by Castille Landon.
As a shocking truth about a couple's families emerges, the two lovers
discover they are not so different from each other.
Tessa is no longer the sweet, simple, good girl she was when she met Hardin —
any more than he is the cruel, moody boy she fell so hard for.
Tessa Young, played by Josephine Langford.
Hardin Scott, played by Hero Fiennes Tiffin.
Robert, played by Carter Jenkins.
Trish Daniels, played by Louise Lombard.
Landon Gibson, played by Chance Perdomo.
Ken Scott, played by Rob Estes.
After Ever Happy (released in some countries as After Ever After and After Forever) is a 2022 American romantic drama film
directed by Castille Landon from a screenplay by Sharon Soboil, based on the 2015 novel of the same name by Anna Todd.
It is the sequel to After We Fell (2021) and the fourth
installment in the After film series.
The film stars Josephine Langford and Hero Fiennes Tiffin reprising
their roles as Tessa Young and Hardin Scott, respectively.
The film was shot back-to-back in Bulgaria in 2020
with its predecessor, After We Fell.
After Ever Happy was released in Italy on August 22, 2022, in Europe from August 24, 2022,
and was released in the United States on September 7, by Voltage Pictures.
Like its predecessors, it received negative reviews.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, love, teenage crush.
The tone is emotional.